AS YOU STOOD BY
EUN-SU, HUI-SU AND JANG KANG
Who... who are you?
You need to leave now.
You're calling this in?
What'll you tell the cops?
That you killed your husband,
and he's back now?
Huh?
You're mistaking me for someone else.
Please leave.
Your face healed nicely.
You looked so miserable
that day at the café
when you broke the cup
and spilled ice all over.
You must feel so much better now.
Since you murdered your husband.
I don't know what you're talking about.
- My husband should be home any minute.
- Who? Jin-pyo?
The last time I was here,
I dragged his body out.
Like this, right? It was a challenge.
Jin-pyo in a fucking suitcase.
His body was heavy as hell.
Your place
doesn't smell so perfumy today.
I bet that's where he put the camera.
Yep, looks like the exact angle.
Ooh. That must've hurt.
As soon as you land, toss it.
Stop. Cut it out.
Do you know how much it cost me
to restore this thing?
What are you doing here?
I like this place.
I'd love to see the rest of the house now.
Open it.
I don't know the combination.
Try one.
The password is incorrect.
- The password is incorrect.
- Are you serious?
Open it by tomorrow.
I'll be needing...
three billion won.
What?
You and Jo Eun-su murdered your husband.
You'll want me to keep quiet.
You've got it wrong.
Eun-su had nothing to do with it.
Three billion.
I don't have any money.
Really?
Then I guess I should go talk to Jin-young
down at the police station.
Fun times, huh?
It's my mother-in-law.
She's on her way here.
MOTHER
She said she's planning on
spending the night here.
Having a talk with her
should be interesting.
I thought you wanted money.
Pick up.
Tell her to piss off.
She'll know I'm not okay.
She'll hear it in my voice.
She might call the police.
Oh shit.
Wait. Someone might see you.
Now you're getting it.
It's fine. I'll avoid cameras.
No one will notice me.
You and Jo Eun-su,
you lucked out. You know that?
I can be sneaky.
You have five days.
Huh?
Right.
MOTHER
Hello, Mother.
Sorry I didn't answer. I was washing up.
Did you have a bubble bath or something?
Has Jin-pyo called yet?
No, I haven't heard from him.
All right.
Oh!
I haven't seen you around lately.
Were you away on business?
You know, your mother insisted
I call her the second I saw you.
I've been keeping an eye out.
Sir, I'm so happy to see you.
I'm glad that you've returned.
What do you want?
Like a smoke or some money or...
Goodness, sir! I wouldn't dream of it!
Hey, I forgot something... in the car.
Can you help me?
Sh.
No. Not that way.
Gotta be sneaky, right?
Tell Jo Hui-su her phone is off.
Who is this?
Why are you playing dumb?
You didn't know I was back?
Jang Kang?
Did you miss me?
I'm in Seoul.
- You promised never to come back to Korea.
- Yeah.
I forgot.
I just paid Jo Hui-su a little visit.
Are you insane? You went to her house?
Three billion won. Five days.
Clock's ticking.
HUI-SU
The customer you are calling
is currently unavailable.
Please leave a message after the tone.
- Whoa. Sorry. I can't let you through.
- No, wait. Just one second.
This is a crime scene. It's off limits.
- Settle down, ma'am.
- No, give me a second!
- I told you, you can't pass through.
- Was a woman hurt?
Calm down. Victim's a man.
It's the security guard.
Poor guy was found dead.
HUI-SU
The customer you are calling
is currently unavailable.
Morning, Mr. Jin.
Hui-su's late? That's not like her?
She's taken a load
off your shoulders lately, huh?
- Hi, what's up?
- Yes, hello. Mr. Jin?
- Has Hui-su come in today?
- Not yet.
She's running late.
Okay, and would you happen to know
where Mr. Jang Kang is staying?
Jang Kang?
Yeah, but never mind.
Could you please tell Hui-su
to give me a call when she gets to work?
Thanks so much.
What was that?
Morning, Mr. Jin.
Hey, uh...
Did you hear Jang Kang's back?
Oh? How'd you know?
I heard he got back two days ago,
but I haven't seen him yet.
Sorry, do you have a phone charger?
Yeah. Sure. I'll plug it in.
Oh, uh, it's ringing.
Could I get it back, please?
Of course, no problem.
Hello?
I opened the safe.
Yes.
Mom. Hi.
What's the matter?
What is it?
Come here.
I can't be away too long.
The security guard
at Jin-pyo's place died.
So what?
Look into it.
Ugh, I'm busy.
It's just...
I'd actually asked
that very guard to keep an eye on Hui-su.
Ugh, Ma!
She seems really off to me.
Why would you say that?
- Jin-pyo's the one being weird.
- Hey!
How dare you compare the two!
You don't find it strange that she hasn't
worked in forever and suddenly got a job?
She's been acting like
she doesn't mind he's gone.
Oh, Mom, why are you being like this?
Hui-su!
Where were you? Your phone wasn't on.
Oh.
- Stand clear of closing doors.
- I forgot to plug it in.
God, you should've called last night.
I would've rushed over here.
You've done so much.
You're okay though, right?
Mm-hmm.
Thank God.
This won't be enough for Jang Kang.
So what are you gonna do?
I'll put my mom's house up
for urgent sale.
I'll put this place up too.
I'll get as much money as possible
to get him to leave.
What if he comes back?
What if, after everything you give him,
he comes back to threaten you again?
- I'm gonna meet him and settle this.
- No, please don't.
- How can he ask for three billion won?
- Just stay out of it.
What, Hui-su?
Jang Kang.
He is way more terrifying
than you imagine.
He's the one who
killed that security guard.
The detectives
who came by this morning
already went through
all of Mr. Kim's stuff.
I found something else.
Just now, it was in here.
Pretty sure it was his.
Oh, okay.
Right.
- Hello, sir.
- Yes?
I live in unit 703.
I was wondering about
the pest control scheduled for next week.
Which block are you starting with?
Is there any way my place
could be done before 9:00 a.m.?
Oh, I'm so sorry, ma'am.
We hired a private company to do it,
and it's against building policy
for them to start before 9:00.
Oh? Jin-young.
I get it.
I wouldn't have called 119
about the guard either.
We need to focus on Jang Kang for now.
He can try to blackmail you.
But the truth is,
he has no evidence at all.
There's no way Jin-pyo's phone
will provide his whereabouts. Don't worry.
He can't risk meeting
with Jin-pyo's sister.
The minute he shows his face,
he'll have to give up on the money.
He can't come back here either.
What happened to the guard
was really tragic. I know.
But pretty soon, Jang Kang is gonna have
no other choice but to lay low.
But Eun-su, I--
No, we.
Mm-hmm.
This is my first case since
I transferred to the Violent Crimes Unit.
What a surprise
running into you like this.
I know, right?
I was at my brother's and figured
I should come see about the incident.
Well, um, I'm finding it really strange
the cameras didn't get any images.
Uh, I know the video quality
is never great,
but the drizzle last night
only made it worse.
Here.
You missed this.
What? Oh man!
Where'd you get this? Thanks so much.
Damn. How did I overlook something
so important?
Yes, hello?
- I gotta take this, okay?
- Mm.
Yes, I'm looking into it now.
DELETING FILE
FILE DELETED
Jin-young.
Hmm?
- There isn't much to see, huh?
- Hmm.
Yeah.
The way I see it,
the bastard knows
how to dodge the cameras.
Or the bitch.
What?
Huh?
Oh! You're right!
Yeah, totally.
Man, you really are the best.
Hey, do you have a minute?
Remember what I asked for last time?
Have any alerts come in on that name?
Nothing yet?
So he isn't back in Korea?
Got it. Let's catch up soon.
Later.
Don't come back yet.
Not until I get that promotion.
The customer you are calling
is currently unavailable.
Please leave a message after...
Don't you dare go near Hui-su's place.
Cops are everywhere.
I'll come to you. Pin your location.
MS. KIM MI-GYEONG
Yes, Mrs. Kim?
How about you try it on?
It's lovely.
Hey, listen. I'll be back in a moment.
Cover for me, please.
Are you out of your mind?
This place is packed.
Scared people will think Jin-pyo's here?
Follow me.
Listen, honey.
You think you can give me orders?
You're a killer.
Are you nuts?
Someone's over there watching us.
If you want your money, follow me.
- Hello Eun-su.
- Hello.
Oh, hello.
Are you here to look at necklaces?
Oh, hell yeah.
- Pardon?
- He's kidding around.
This way, sir.
Excuse us.
Take the red-eye to China tonight.
Nah.
Chill out, will ya?
I don't give a damn about Jin-pyo.
He's already dead.
What do you mean he's dead?
Can you prove it?
I knew you wanted to whack the guy.
He beat her, kept her under surveillance,
and tracked her location.
You two thought you were so smart.
Thing is, you had no clue the prick
was tracking his wife's every move.
Huh?
Just give me his phone.
No, I want the money first.
Hand it over, or I'll report you
for murdering the security guard.
So what if you report me?
Think I won't drag you down? Think I won't
tell them about you and your friend?
What would you get from doing that anyway?
If we get arrested, remember,
you won't get any money.
Oh yeah.
I'll adjust my fee to include the phone.
3.1 billion.
This is how scared
you should've been all along.
Shouldn't have underestimated me,
you know?
Ms. Eun-su.
- Yes?
- She's waiting for you.
KO JEONG-SUK’S BY YOUR SIDE
Oh, hello, Mrs. Ko.
It's an honor to meet you.
- Thank you, dear.
- I'm a huge fan of yours.
- Hello.
- I've read all your books.
- I... I love them all.
- So lovely to hear. Thank you.
Oh, I... I just love her.
- Mrs. Ko. I'm such a fan.
- Nice to meet you. Sure.
- It's so wonderful to meet you.
- Yes.
May I take a picture with you?
Of course.
You know, my friend,
her marriage has improved so much
thanks to you.
But unfortunately,
she couldn't make it today.
- I see. Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
- Hello, Mrs. Ko.
- I'm such a fan.
- Hello.
- Thank you.
- Yes. Thank you for coming.
- Of course.
Mom, I'm on the run.
Where are you?
I'm out of money, Mom.
I need you to send me some.
For the most part,
these remarks only worsen the relationship
rather than resolve the problem.
Why do you think that is?
It's because we fail to understand
the other person's intention
and focus instead
on their choice of words.
Conversation is the process
of understanding each other's intentions.
But we often start to talk
in a defensive mood.
A married couple
is the beating heart of the family.
If we understand
how the other expresses themselves.
And keep that in mind during
the more challenging conversations...
You need to keep me
and the money a secret.
And don't text back. I'll be in touch.
...that communicate effectively
with each other
and share activities and experiences
will have received
the world's greatest gift.
- Hey, lady.
- Everyone, please...
Keep this secret.
- It's our secret. Okay?
- It begins with one remark.
It is crucial to learn
how to listen, empathize with,
and understand each other's intentions.
Um, Mr. Chairman,
do you think you can perhaps refer me
to a trustworthy agency
to handle something?
It's not for me.
I'm asking for a client I care for.
Certainly.
Safe travels, sir.
Hey, Jang Kang. You're here.
You really came back, huh?
Mr. Wi.
If you were gonna come back so soon,
why'd you leave at all?
And, um, where are you staying now?
Oh, hey, hey, hey.
Come here. Taste some of this.
Here. Have a bite, yeah?
It's on me, okay? Eat up.
Ah, don't mention it. It's been ages.
I'll give you a sundae too.
Ma'am, a sundae for my friend.
Ha. Here.
- Eat up.
- I don't want any.
Give me the bill, lady.
Wh... what?
Keep the change.
It'll cover whatever this guy orders.
Hey, Wi.
- We should get a drink.
- Uh... Oh, okay.
Hey, go easy on them, huh?
- This guy's a shark.
- He's an expert.
Hey, those look good.
Mr. Ma, the manager
of the private detective agency,
isn't here today.
If he shows up,
tell him that if a Jo Eun-su should call,
he should assign his best guy to the job.
Jo Eun-su?
Sir, it's your turn now.
You're here, sir.
That guy used to move boxes
at your warehouse, right?
He was totally out of control,
so I left him there to drink
till he passed out.
I'm guessing he came into some money.
Why couldn't he just have
a few drinks and take it easy?
I just finished redecorating the place.
This is terrible.
- This should cover the damage.
- Thank you.
He used to save the broth
for instant noodles for later.
Now he's handing out
50,000 won bills to escorts.
He used to call me "sir" out of respect.
Now he buys the drinks and acts so rude.
I get it.
He's supposed to score
three billion won really soon,
so this kind of money
is like a joke to him now.
Three billion?
He mentioned
these two bitches that owe him.
I mean, he's got two women
wrapped around his finger,
and they're gonna give him
the three billion.
He's obviously scamming
or blackmailing them, sir.
Oh shit.
Mr. Jin.
What the fuck?
Who do you think you are?
You think you can put your hands
on my money?
Huh?
You wrecked the place.
You need to pay, jackass.
Also,
you're in some new business, huh?
You wouldn't want the cops to come get you
for entering the country illegally.
Fuck, man.
What makes you think I got in illegally?
I have a passport. Actually, I have two.
There's mine and another guy's.
Make this fucking asshole pay
for the damage and give me my cash now.
Now!
Huh?
Watch it.
See you when you sober up, loser.
Let's go.
- Yes, sir.
- Where the fuck do you think you're going?
Fucking hell.
That's for messing
with one of my employees.
Fuck. Dammit!
Hey!
Fuck you!
Fuck!
Could you step out a minute?
- Yes, hello?
- Hi, sir.
Sorry for not coming in. I'm still sick.
- You in trouble or something?
- Not at all, sir. I'm fine.
Okay, then. Mm.
Take care.
Come in when you're better. Okay?
Password is incorrect.
Tell him that
if a Jo Eun-su should call,
he should assign his best guy to the job.
Jo Eun-su?
MS. JO EUN-SU
She should've
killed her husband.
What can they do
if there's no body to prove it?
Make sure no one knows you did it,
or make sure no one knows he's dead.
That's why Eun-su hired Jang Kang.
Where's Hui-su's husband?
I have a passport.
Actually, I have two.
There's mine and another guy's.
Does your husband know
you're applying here?
We're separated.
No, she thought of that because of me.
Hey, Mr. Ma. Have you eaten yet?
Yeah.
Sir, could you get some intel on someone?
A location tracker?
Good news is I don't think Jang Kang
knows where Jin-pyo's body is.
We need to get that phone from him
before he figures it out.
How though?
Give me a sec.
Hello, I called a little earlier today.
I need to retrieve a phone.
There are eyes everywhere.
Just tell me where you are.
I'll bring you the money.
- Yeah, no. Call me later.
- Are you at your old place?
Fuck me. I said call later!
MANAGER HWANG
Please start
by looking into motels in this area.
SAN 1, DAECHI-RI, HYEONBUK-MYEON,
YANGYANG-GUN, GANGWON-DO
LOCATION TRACKER
CONNECTION LOST
WOULD YOU LIKE TO RECONNECT?
NO RECORDS LOCATIONS
OCTOBER 30
That afternoon...
...she went there before Jin-pyo died.
What was she doing out there?
SAN 1, DAECHI-RI
Yeah, I found the motel,
but the man just got a cab and left.
Looks like he was in a hurry.
Want me to keep following him, ma'am?
Please do that.
He just took the Gangneung exit
at the Yangyang junction.
- Should I stay on his tail?
- At Yangyang?
No, you can stop there.
Thank you. That'll be all for now.
Ms. Jo's been trying to get her
hands on Jang Kang's phone.
But out of nowhere, she asked us to stop
tailing him in the middle of the highway.
Sir, would you like me
to keep an eye on him?
Uh-huh.
Without Eun-su knowing.
Processing.
Please wait.
Transaction complete.
Please take your cash.
Never use an ATM if it appears
to have been tampered with.
Hey Hui-su. I have a work thing,
so I'll be out of reach
for the next few hours.
Did you get the phone back?
Not yet, but soon, I hope.
Hey. If Jang Kang calls you today,
don't pick up, okay?
- He's gonna call though.
- Just don't pick up. I'll handle the guy.
Jo Eun-su.
Guess where.
Huh?
Yeah, Yangyang.
Mount Manwol in Yangyang.
I bet Jin-pyo's here.
He's here, isn't he? Huh?
Hey.
What'd you think of the video I sent?
Looks like a random mountain to me.
I guess you girls worked really hard
to bury him in that random mountain. Huh?
I know what I'll do.
I'll bring a shovel and stuff
to go dig up there tomorrow.
I wonder what I'll find.
Sounds like fun.
I have the money though.
You wanna meet?
She looked like
she really needed money.
Seems a shame
to sell that place for so little.
ACE REAL ESTATE
I added another lock
to my front door just in case.
Here's the key. Go wait at my house.
Uh... let's go together
when you get off work.
Uh, I'm working late tonight.
I think we've been letting our guard down.
Jang Kang might show up again.
Yeah, but I'm not sure
I should go there alone.
Are you the new replacement?
Mr. Hwang asked me
to handle your case from now on.
If you tell me Jang Kang's whereabouts,
I'll find the guy and see
that he's back in China by tomorrow.
I'll be standing by
at the location you specified.
Jin-pyo?
That's not him.
He isn't back in Korea.
Is this a fuckin' joke?
What the hell
am I supposed to do with this?
She'll put the rest in that bag later.
How much are we talkin'?
We're gonna have to count it.
Hui-su found it under the mattress
when she cleaned out her mom's place.
Could be ten times that.
No wonder she's in a loony bin,
pulling shit like that.
How much longer?
A while still.
INSPECTOR CHOI GYEONG-GU
What's up, Choi?
Yeah, hi. Uh, well,
I've been reviewing the evidence
for the security guard's case.
Huh?
Uh... good. That's great. You're killing it.
Thanks, but the thing is, uh,
the dashcam footage that we managed
to get from a car
that drove by around then...
There's no easy way to say it,
but it captured your sister-in-law.
What?
What are you trying to insinuate?
Uh, no, nothing much.
I didn't mean anything by it.
It's just that she was standing there,
and I found it a bit odd.
So I thought I'd call and check with you.
Uh, listen, I'm driving now.
Okay, I see. Sorry.
I'll call you later, Jin-young.
All right, goodbye.
Oh shit.
I've got the interview tomorrow.
Gotta get rid of the dashcam footage.
MOM
- Mom, can I call you back? I'm busy--
- Your brother was here.
He has some terrible people after him.
He came to see me,
but he had to keep his distance.
Anyway, find your brother
and bring him home
before his office gets to him.
I've been rereading his messages
for the past two days.
I'm worried sick.
Messages?
MOM, I'M ON THE RUNN
I'M OUT OF MONEE
NOONE CAN NO ABOUT THE MONEE OR ME
JIN-PYO
I'M HAVING DINNER WITH MOM TONIGHT
YOU CAN MAKE IT, RIGHT?
Jin-pyo didn't send any of these.
Where are we?
We almost there?
Hey.
How much longer till we get there?
Where are we going?
Huh?
Let me out.
Just stop the car!
- Let go!
- Fucking bitch!
Stop it!
You fucking whore!
You bitch!
I told you to pull over.
You almost got us both killed. Huh? Huh?
I could kill you right now.
But I want my fucking money.
Pay up or die.
Wait!
Get the fuck off me!
Where the fuck are we?